Good Morning, Church!
You see me every day, and still, each time you see me, you start screaming.
I am supposed to scream too because I usually see you occasionally...
Not all the time I used to see you...
But you see me every day - every time you see me, you still scream...
The SCOAN Sunday Service
What will I believe now? Will I believe this screaming?
Will I believe all this screaming and close my eyes? - I have to open one eye.
This your screaming every day!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
I understand. You are inspired.
You may be seated. Thank you.
You are inspired.
I know that when one is inspired, you just see him laughing whereas there is nothing to laugh about.
Happy Mother's Day!
Hallelujah!
I thank God that I am not alone here.
If I was alone, I would feel shy.
I am not alone; I am in the midst of millions of people.
Can you see any one of them?
There are millions of people here. I'm not alone. That is why when you scream, I'm not moved.
Hallelujah. I was dancing and rejoicing with you. I watched testimonies.
It got to a stage when the Lord said, "Go out, it is time for you to attend to the people".
I said, "Lord, thank You".
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Do we still have anyone that is going through satan's torture?
Satan tortures people with worry about now and the future.
When you are under that, you are under torture.
You understand what I´m saying? You may not know what I am talking about when I say,
"Do we have anyone that is going through satan's torture?"
That is when you begin to think, "I'm worried";
"Will I be healed?"; "How will I pay that debt?";
"When are we leaving here? I think I will not miss my flight."
So anxious and desperate.
A lot of people have been dancing.
You look around and see some of your neighbours - they refused to dance
because maybe, they are waiting for their testimony.
They say, "Until I have my testimony, I will not dance".
If you are waiting for your own testimony, definitely, that testimony may never come
because the pain of one is the pain of all, and the joy of one is the joy of all. Tell your neighbour.
The pain of one is the pain of all, and the joy of one is the joy of all.
I can´t hear you.
As a Christian, when you see your neighbour happy, join them.
You don't need to wait until you are happy.
You say, "They are giving testimony - until it happens to me!"
Some people just believe that, "Something must happen to me. If it has happened to me, it has happened.
If it has not happened to me, it has not happened".
They say, "Oh no, testimony. I am waiting for my own testimony".
That is not a good language for Christians.
The question I am even asking is, "Are you going through satan's torture?
So anxious, sad, depressed, worried about now and the future?"
"How will I be healed? I mean, I´m owing debt."
"My marriage, my health, my career!" - so anxious.
In the book of Matthew 4:2, our Saviour, after 40 days and 40 nights,
He was hungry but not desperate.
No, he was very, very hungry.
Very, very hungry, after 40 days, 40 nights, but not desperate, not anxious.
Because He was not anxious, that is why He did not fall into satan's trap.
Jesus did not fall into satan's trap because He was not what? - He was not desperate.
But today, many...
When you act so desperate, you will not mind where solution comes from.
When you are desperate, you will not mind God's time and God's time is the best.
"No, I just need it now. I'm so and so. I´m looking for a job. No, I don´t mind."
- when you are desperate, anxious.
Are you going through that?
God's time is the best. Tell your neighbour.
God's time is the best.
I can´t hear you.
At God's time, things look beautiful.
The right time.
When you receive something at God's time, it lasts forever.
What you need most, it´s there.
Don't be desperate. Tell your neighbour.
Don't be desperate.
I can´t hear you...
The language of people that are desperate is, "I'm waiting for my testimony".
When they see people rejoice, they look to the other side.
They look to the other side, when they see people in church.
"Oh, why are you dancing?"
"Oh, testimony. I too have the same issue. I´m waiting for my own testimony."
That is when you´ll be happy.
Oh.
You have to rejoice with those who rejoice.
If not, your day of joy may never what? - May never come.
Each message is life-changing.
I am happy because you are happy..
Are you not happy?
Because I´m seeing you happy. You say what?
You're happy. You should not wait until it has happened to you, okay?
When you see your colleagues happy because of what God has done,
that is testimony for you.
What happens to your colleague is meant to build your faith.
What happened to me is meant to build your faith
and what happened to you is also meant to build my faith.
God is great!
Hallelujah!
We want to go to the sick ones.
Each issue brings revelation.
And as we share it together, we learn.
Like I have said, what will happen to anyone here is meant to build your faith;
it enhances your faith.
So when people say, "Thank You Jesus!",
you are looking to see what happened to the person before you say, "Thank You, Jesus!"
That is why you say: "Thank You, Jesus!"
When you now see what happens, you say, "Thank You, Jesus!"
It is time to attend to them.
Viewers at home, I know you will see acts of mercy of God today;
acts of healing of God - you will see them clearly, in Jesus' name.
Thank you.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
What is going on in your heart when you see people with bandages, braces, this and that?
I believe strongly that they have an appointment with God today and God is going to work.
Their pain is your pain.
Yes.
When you see their pain, it is your pain.
So when we start praying, you join us in prayer as well.
Yes.
When I say, "Be healed!", your heart too should say, "Be healed!"
Yes, Man of God.
When the person is healed, it means your prayer and my prayer made it happen.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
What does it mean to you when you see people with different gadgets?
Man of God, like you said, it means that man is born into trouble.
Man is born into trouble.
Yes.
Ah, I´m afraid of you!
This man! Your word is pregnant.
Let me ask again. I don't know what he wants to say again.
Man of God...
Ah! In each word, you keep saying "Man of God".
Yes.
Why can't you go straight to the point?
You said, "Man of God, man is born into trouble". Am I the one that born you into trouble?
Man of God, that is why you are sent to us
because Christ is in you and you are in Christ.
But you too. You are sent to me.
Man of God, each time I see you, I see Christ in you.
Each time I see you, I see Christ with a crown.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
My brother, you have said it all. He said, "Man is born into trouble".
Each time you are facing challenges, you should know it is a way of life.
Stop saying "witches and wizards" instead of facing it.
Man is born into trouble.
Thank you very much. Clap for him.
So sister, how does the whole thing appeal to you?
Like their pain is my pain.
I should put myself in their position.
Put yourself in their position.
Yes.
When it is time for prayer, what is your position?
To pray for them too.
You pray; you join us in prayer.
Amen.
When the miracle happens, you know your prayer has been answered.
Viewers at home, join me in prayer.
So when I stretch my hand, if you cannot stretch your hand, stretch your heart.
When I say, "In Jesus' name!", you too say after me, "In Jesus' name!"
And when the miracle happens, it happens because two believers are better than one.
Man of God, I experience difficulty in walking due to degeneration of disc disease.
I´m using a lumbar corset and lumbar body support to help me suppress the pain.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
So you use a lot of tablets.
To suppress the pain.
So it is time to pray, ok?
So this is a Spirit prayer.
Prayer in the power of the Holy Ghost.
Be delivered, in Jesus' name!
Healing in Jesus' Name
You are confirming yourself now. Thank You, Lord. Come on. Stand up.
I have shortness of breath.
I have been using a breathing machine to assist me with my breathing for two years now.
From where?
I´m from South Africa.
What is this?
It's an oxygen machine.
So you came with her?
Yes.
Ok, it's alright. Stand at the back.
Healing in Jesus' Name
Stand up.
Remove it.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Your heart. Ok?
Healing in Jesus' Name
Ok.
Healed In Jesus' Name
Thank You, Jesus!
I can breathe now without machine.
Healed In Jesus' Name
My lungs are free.
Thank You, Jesus!
Healing In Jesus' Name
Healed In Jesus' Name
Thank You, Jesus! I can walk now. I can walk very well.
Healing In Jesus' Name
Thank You, Jesus!
Thank You, Jesus! I am free! I can use my hands!
I cannot walk and stand well.
Healing In Jesus' Name
Thank You, Jesus! I can walk again!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Come here! Go this way!
Healed In Jesus' Name
The SCOAN Sunday Service
I have difficulty in breathing due to asthma and sleep apnea.
Please help me, Man of God. This is the nebuliser that I use; it helps me to breathe.
Ok, it's alright.
Healing In Jesus' Name
I can do exercise now. I won´t breathe like a kitten anymore!
Healed In Jesus' Name
I can walk now! Thank You, Jesus!
Healing In Jesus' Name
Healed In Jesus' Name
Thank You, Jesus! I am free!
Healing In Jesus' Name
Healed In Jesus' Name
Thank You, Jesus! I am free!
Healing In Jesus' Name
Healed In Jesus' Name
Touch me!
Healing In Jesus' Name
Healed In Jesus' Name
I'm from America. I use this machine because I am suffering from high blood pressure,
gout, and hemorrhoids. I can´t sleep without this machine.
The doctor told me that if I don't use this machine, I will become paralysed and will die.
Healing In Jesus' Name
I am free! Thank You, Jesus!
Healed In Jesus' Name
I am free! I can breathe well!
I can breathe.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Healing In Jesus' Name
Come on!
Please help me!
Healing In Jesus' Name
Healed Of Anus Cancer In Jesus' Name
I can sit now!
Yes, he can sit now!
I can sit! Now I can sit!
Healed Of Anus Cancer In Jesus' Name
Ok. To God be the glory! This is a brother who had the problem of anus cancer.
The doctors condemned my anus and on Thursday I was supposed to go for the third operation.
They said it was cancer of the anus and they would open part of my belly,
where I would be passing out my faeces a lifetime.
So, I left the hospital on Wednesday. From Bayelsa, I had to come to Lagos.
What happened to you now that caused this amazement? You're so surprised.
After the prayers, I am healed; I can sit now.
What about the pain?
The pain - it's gone!
Can you sit now? Sit and tell us...
Thank You, Jesus!
We thank God for His goodness in the life of the young man here.
You heard him. He said he has undergone two major operations
and he was booked for a third operation, before he proceeded on the journey to The SCOAN.
He said he could not sit at all for the past one year.
But after the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua, touched him, he said the pain is gone.
For the first time in one year, he is sitting now, to the glory of God.
God of T.B. Joshua, thank You!
You heard this man saying that he had not slept for one year. See him sleeping.
That is to show that he received a touch of God, in Jesus' name.